playu.net 2008-02-12

# iDotz.Net - Domain Name Registrar: Cool Domains @ Great Prices!

  **iDotz.Net™ Privacy Policy  
   **(effective July 1, 2002) 

  This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our Web site or by otherwise interacting with dotFM, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. For questions on the Privacy Policy please contact 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net).

  Your privacy is very important to iDotz.Net, a division on BRS Media Inc., which owns all information collected from the site and is a registrar of domain names. iDotz.Net also offers other supplementary products and services (the "Service"). We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement describes how we collect information, how we use the information we collect, and to whom and under what conditions we may disclose this information. This statement reflects our concern with your privacy. Please understand that the following statement applies to www.idot.net only. 

  When you use our Service, iDotz.Net asks for your first and last name, organization, city, state, zip code (or country and postal code for non-U.S. residents), telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information. We may use this personally identifiable information to contact you about your account or other matters relating to the Service, such as to inform you about new features on our Site. We may also use this personally identifiable information to send you our newsletter or e-mail messages regarding products or services we think you might be interested in. (See below for instructions on how you can "opt out" of our newsletter or these e-mail messages.) These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality products and services that are responsive to your needs. At the same time, these communications, and your responses to them, give us helpful insights about you, your preferences and the ways in which we might improve our services. We therefore may maintain this information for future use. When you utilize the Service, we may also ask you for a "screen name." Although we may not use it now, the screen name you select may appear on the web site in connection with future services we provide. 

  Like many other commercial web sites, our Site employs a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our Site is used, such as which pages are the most frequently visited by our customers. "Cookies" are small pieces of electronic information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide personalized information and features such as pre-populated address forms and storage of selected items in your Shopping Cart between visits. Cookies are required for normal website functionality, and most web browsers automatically accept cookies, although you can usually change your browser to deactivate cookies by modifying your computer browser preferences. If you choose to deactivate cookies, please note that deactivation of cookies will sometimes hinder your ability to use some features available from the Service. Through the use of cookies, we take note of whether and how you use the information and services that we provide, such as by recording site traffic patterns and by maintaining log files of your access to various parts of the Site. We may collect the information passed along by your web browser that references the Web URL you linked from, the time, type of web browser being used, screen size, Internet speed of connection, the operating system/platform, and CPU speed. This information may be used to identify demographic trends and to provide information tailored to your interests. 

  Cookies may also be utilized by third parties who advertise or provide links on the Site. Due to the way the Internet technically operates, iDotz.Net cannot the control data collection activities by such third-party advertisers or linked web sites. You should contact these advertisers or web site operators if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect. Also, if you register a domain name through another registrar, you may receive a cookie from that registrar, but you will not receive a cookie from us. 

Registrants may elect not to receive e-mail communications from iDotz.Net regarding other products or services provided by iDotz.Net or BRS Media Inc. To do so, please send an email to 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net) that reads, "Remove from E-mail List." You can also fax us at +1 (415) 677-4025 or send us mail at:

BRS Media Inc.  
Attention: iDotz.Net Opting Out  
55 New Montgomery St. Suite 622  
San Francisco, CA 94105-3432

 iDotz.Net understands that security is important to our users. The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. When you transmit personal information to us, we encrypt it using SSL (Secure Socket Layer), the industry standard for encryption software. Encryption provides a secure means to protect your information as it passes over the web to our server. iDotz.Net utilizes Thawte SSL Web Server Certificates to offer secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the site. You can verify this certificate by clicking here: 

iDotz.Net Certificate

 iDotz.Net will use commercially available and acceptable means to protect any information you provide, but cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us from our products and services, and you do so at your own risk. iDotz.Net will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

  As the registrar of domain names, we may make certain information about you available to the general public via our domain name look-up and directory "whois" service (e.g., name, address, telephone and email of the Registrant). Additionally, we may share the information stored on that database, as well as other information we collect or you provide, with our subsidiaries and other parties selected by us, including with the parties or circumstances including, but not limited to: 

   · Agents or vendors who are responsible for handling your Account or performing  
     other necessary service that you or we require. 

   · Business partners whose services you may request or access on or through our  
     Site. 

   · Business partners or vendors who we believe offer products or services that may  
     be of interest to you. 

   · Transfer of ownership of our business or a part of our business. If our business  
     or a part of our business is acquired, sold or transferred to another business,  
     customer information may be a part of that acquisition, sale or transfer. 

 _Protection of iDotz.Net and Others_ : We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable account information if required to do so by law, subpoena, search warrant, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, including ICANN; to enforce or apply our Services Agreement or other agreements; or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of BRS Media Inc., iDotz.Net, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 If you do not want us to share personally identifiable information about you with our business partners or vendors, you may send us e-mail at 

[ privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net). You may not opt out from having your personal information displayed in our "whois" database.

  We may enter into agreements to allow third party registrars of domain. When users register domain names through these third party registrars, we will transfer the registration information collected during the registration process to the domain Registry. We may also be required to submit this information to ICANN (Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers), or other regulatory bodies.

  Although iDotz.Net is committed to protecting your privacy, not all other Web sites are as conscientious. Therefore, iDotz.Net cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of other Web sites including those of advertisers to which it may link and those which link to iDotz.Net. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected by this Web site. We ask that you review the privacy policies of every online service you use before submitting personal information. 

  We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, please feel free to send us an e-mail at 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net) or by mail at:

BRS Media Inc.  
Attention: iDotz.Net Privacy Policy  
55 New Montgomery St. Suite 622  
San Francisco, CA 94105-3432
